Hi everyone, this is EYA on EYA Censored
Supernatural Bible Changes on YouTube
and today is Sunday the 12th of April
2026.
In this video, I want to touch upon
what's happening in the Middle East.
This is a headline um in Daily Mail,
Traffic in the Strait of Hormuz. It goes
on to say, Into the Kill Zone, Trump
orders US sailors to seize Hormuz after
he destroyed Iran's navy, but shadow
fleet still lies in wait.
And um so of course we know there's a
lot happening in the Middle East and it
really is quite prophetic of course.
But what I want to focus on the rest of
our time
um
tonight going through this video is
talking about how this correlates with
what we're seeing happen in scripture.
Our Bibles are under satanic assault and
supernaturally changing. I've been
covering these nefarious wicked
self-evident changes since July of 2016
on YouTube and um I continue to be as
passionate about sharing the truth of
what's happening to the Bible as I did
the first video that I did.
And um I'm going to go ahead and show
you how this this this particular
headline correlates with the madness
that we're seeing happen to the Bible.
Now I want to also preface this by
saying that Jesus is the Christ the Son
of God. He is the King of Kings and Lord
of Lords. We know that to be true. He is
the word of God according to John 1:1
and Revelations 19:13.
Our Bibles however are being satanically
changed to prepare the way for the
Antichrist and coming one world satanic
system. It is absolutely the abomination
of desolation standing in the holy
place.
And he who reads let him understand and
I'm reading and I understand and I see
the changes that are happening to our to
our Bibles. Let me go ahead and show you
this is actually a KJV index that I put
together. This is found on my website
bible-changes.com
and I have over 7,000 verses already
gathered since today on what's happening
to our Bibles and I want to go ahead and
show you that the word straight is a new
word in the Bible. That's right,
straight. What a ridiculous
way to spell straight. But it is in our
Bibles now.
Here we have it showing 11 times in 12
12 times in 11 verses. I'm going to go
ahead and just show you these are the
scripture verses and I'm only going to
focus on a couple here but you should
read all of them. And keep in mind that
when I highlight a word, it doesn't mean
that's the only change in that
particular verse. There could be
multiple changes, whether it's grammar
errors, spelling errors, punctuation
errors, uh new words, words omitted, new
people, right? New countries, new
places, emoticons even. These are the
things that we're seeing throughout
scripture today and it's absolutely
diabolical.
Um but I want to go ahead and focus on
some verses that you might be familiar
with that were hidden in your heart. And
this has to do with um you know, enter
the narrow gate. Right? For broad is the
road that leads to destruction and few
are those who find it. That's how I
remember that verse. But now we see in
Matthew 7:13 it reads, Enter ye. That's
right, enter ye into in at the strait
gate as opposed to what? A crooked gate?
What does that even mean? For wide is
the gate and broad is the way that
leadeth to destruction.
And many there be which go in thereat.
[clears throat]
This is so hard to read because it's
been changed and the word which has been
uh switched with the word who.
And then thereat is just an absurd new
word but what is a strait gate, right?
What is a strait gate? And then the next
verse is rather odd. It's literally the
next verse and it says, Because strait
is the gate and narrow is the way which
leadeth unto life and few there be that
find it. Again, you can hear even as I'm
reading this to you that it sounds
jagged because they've added words to
this verse.
But again, what is a strait gate, right?
Well, let me go ahead and read another
one. Actually, Luke 13:24 is another
example of this, Strive to enter into
the strait gate. I guess again as
opposed to what? A swirvy gate
or a um an iron gate or a wooden gate? I
mean, what are they even saying? Strait
gate is just absolutely bizarre.
Philippians 1:23 now says this, For I am
in a strait
betwixt two. That's right, for I am in a
strait
betwixt two having a desire to depart
and be with Christ which is far better.
Again, this passage is added and it's
nonsense. Again, the word straight is
new in the Bible. We even have
straighten
um straighteneth.
Again, all new words in the Bible. I'm
going to go ahead and close
[clears throat] that and we even have
the word straightness.
That's right, straightness
is now um in the King James Bible,
straightness. I'm not going to read
those to you but you can do that later.
Then I want to show you that in Matthew
7:13 in all the other Bibles, it does
say enter through the narrow gate. I was
never an NIV reader by the way.
Um but I'm just showing you that other
translations still say enter by the
narrow gate.
And that's how I remember the Berean
Standard Bible and by the way, the word
Berean is erased from the Bible.
Um but I wanted to point that out to
you. Let me know what you remember. Do
you remember like I do, enter the narrow
gate for broad is the road that leads to
destruction? That's what I remember and
I hold to be true. Never straight is the
gate. That's just ludicrous. Moving
along, I want to show you that the word
navy is now found in the King James
Bible twice
in 1 Kings 10:11 and 1 Kings 10:22.
And I'm going to read 1 Kings 10:22 with
to you because it's filled with a lot of
new words that are ridiculous. For the
king had at I got to be careful when I'm
reading this because it's so strange to
even say. It doesn't even come out
naturally. For the king had at sea
a navy of Tharshish with a navy of
Hiram. Once in three years came the navy
of Tharshish
bringing gold and silver, ivory and apes
and peacocks.
How crazy is that that we now have even
apes and peacocks now in the King James
Bible. We also have navy of ships found
in 1 Kings 9:26
and King Solomon made a navy of ships.
I've never heard of Ezion-geber
which is beside Eloth on the shore of
the Red Sea. And notice friends how the
word Red Sea used to always be
capitalized but now only the word Red is
capitalized. And yes, these changes will
be found
in your paper Bible and you need to go
check and and really search out this
matter because this absolutely
happening. It's obvious.
Moving along, I want to show you that we
have presidents in the Bible five times.
Daniel now is one of three presidents.
That's right, one of three presidents.
Absolutely ridiculous.
We also have the new word sailors.
That's right, sailors in the Bible one
time in Revelations 18:17.
And that's obviously a new word in the
Bible in Revelations 18:17 but we also
have the new words of shipmaster
and ships. Those are also new words in
the King James Bible.
Moving along, I want to show you that we
even have um
the word ships is now in the Bible
um 110
times in the King James Bible. We even
have little ships in the Bible.
And on and on it goes. And if you
remember, there's a story of Jesus when
he fell asleep in the boat. Do you
remember that? Um and his disciples got
scared because the wind was so great and
I'm going to go ahead and read Mark 4:38
to you and this is what it says today in
the King James Bible. And he was in the
hinder part of the ship.
Yeah, that's also new. Asleep on a
pillow. That's right, now Jesus sleeps
with his head on a pillow. Again, I
don't know if it's down, if it's
polyester, if it's silk, I'm not sure
but he had his head on a pillow in the
hinder part of the ship. That's
ridiculous.
And then he called master, they called
him teacher, okay? But anyway, um yeah,
lots of changes here. Moving along, I
want to show you that the word Iran is
now in these Bibles right here. I want
to show you in the Amplified Version
which is obviously already changing. You
see we have it in Ezekiel 38:5, it says
Persia. I always remember Persia in the
Bible
in parens called Iran, Cush. I remember
Cush now called Ethiopia and Put. And
then we see we have Libya in North
Africa. All these are new countries in
the Bible.
So, that's what I wanted to share with
you. I do want to remind you of my
website Supernatural Bible Changes. Um
you can find it at bible-changes.com.
I absolutely want to show you this new
feature on my website. I just loaded it
up today and it's crazy new KJV verses.
And I'm going to go ahead and show you
what this looks like.
This has over um 200
changed scripture verses and you can
just scroll through here and start
reading them.
And these changes are obvious
if you have eyes to see. Do you have
eyes to see? Do you have ears to hear?
Do these changes that I'm pointing out
make sense to you?
Because what I can tell you is when I
read the Bible today, it's nonsense.
Page after page, verse after verse,
blasphemy is being poured out in
scripture. And the mainstream church is
quiet
about it.
Saying nothing, not warning
the church, not warning the masses of
what's happening to our Bibles.
And yet it's been clearly altered.
Do you see the changes?
Do not fear, my friends.
Here's what I want you to know. God
loves you. He is faithful. He warned us
of this hour. He told us in the best way
that he could
to be
alert and sober.
So, be strong and courageous, brothers
and sisters. Do not fear or be dismayed,
for the Lord your God is with you
wherever you go. Until next time. Again,
I want to quickly just say that you can
find this list on my website. You can
find it right here. If you go to my
homepage, biblechanges.com,
and you can go to my menu, and there's
the crazy new Bible verses, also
examples, and then this is the index
link right here.
All right, everybody. God bless each and
every one of you, and I look forward to
talking to you soon.